[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the English name of the Mosi-oa-Tunya waterfall located between Zambia and Zimbabwe?", "correct_answer": "Victoria Falls", "incorrect_answers": ["Virginia Falls", "Veronica Falls", "Valeria Falls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Telly Savalas turned down the role of Archer J. Maggott in The Dirty Dozen due to health reasons.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What phobia is referred as fear of houses?", "correct_answer": "Domatophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Dishabiliophobia", "Dysmorphophobia", "Doraphobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of milk is Brie cheese traditionally made of?", "correct_answer": "Cows milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Sheep milk", "Goats milk", "Buffalo milk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What texture does Parmigiano-Reggiano, or parmesan cheese have?", "correct_answer": "Hard", "incorrect_answers": ["Creamy", "Semi-hard", "Soft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which layer of the atmosphere do artificial satellites operate?", "correct_answer": "Low Earth Orbit", "incorrect_answers": ["Medium Earth Orbit", "Elliptic Orbit", "High Earth Orbit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A King Cobra and a frog would be subjects of study of what science?", "correct_answer": "herpetology", "incorrect_answers": ["autecology", "astacology", "reptology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first name of Dr. Greene from the popular television series ER, played by actor Anthony Edwards?", "correct_answer": "Mark", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter", "John", "Richard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which body of water, situated in Southern Siberia, is the deepest and oldest freshwater lake on Earth?", "correct_answer": "Baikal", "incorrect_answers": ["Onega", "Ladoga", "Huron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bathing in what type of water is proven to battle depression and enhance the mood?", "correct_answer": "Cold water", "incorrect_answers": ["Hot water", "Mineral water", "Water with temperature close to that of the human body"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actors Patrick Swayze, Jennifer Gray, Charlie Sheen and C.Thomas Howell played in both Red Dawn and The Outsiders.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year were Thylacines classified as extinct?", "correct_answer": "1986", "incorrect_answers": ["1979", "1974", "1965"]}]